export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: "How old was Bilbo when he set out for Erebor?",
        optionA: "28",
        optionB: "111",
        optionC: "50",
        optionD: "44",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What was Gandalf's name in Valinor?",
        optionA: "Olorin",
        optionB: "Curunir",
        optionC: "Mairon",
        optionD: "Eonwe",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Who was Gimli's father?",
        optionA: "Fili",
        optionB: "Bombur",
        optionC: "Thorin",
        optionD: "Gloin",
        answer: "optionD"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Where did Durin the Deathless awaken?",
        optionA: "Mount Doom",
        optionB: "Mount Gundabad",
        optionC: "Khazad-dum",
        optionD: "Belegost",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which king of Rohan had the epithet 'Hammerhand'?",
        optionA: "Grima",
        optionB: "Helm",
        optionC: "Theoden",
        optionD: "Eomer",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What was the name of the first dragon?",
        optionA: "Glaurung",
        optionB: "Ancalagon",
        optionC: "Smaug",
        optionD: "Gothmog",
        answer: "optionA"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of the Valar was the last to descend to Arda?",
        optionA: "Niennna",
        optionB: "Mandos",
        optionC: "Tulkas",
        optionD: "Varda",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt: "What city did Turgon found?",
        optionA: "Nargothrond",
        optionB: "Nogrod",
        optionC: "Gondolin",
        optionD: "Menegroth",
        answer: "optionC"
    },
    {
        prompt: "Where was Frodo originally from?",
        optionA: "Hobbiton",
        optionB: "Buckland",
        optionC: "Tuckborough",
        optionD: "Michel Delving",
        answer: "optionB"
    },
    {
        prompt: "In which battle was Azog slain?",
        optionA: "Dagor Bragollach",
        optionB: "Battle of the Five Armies",
        optionC: "Battle of Azanulbizar",
        optionD: "Battle of the Pelennor Fields",
        answer: "optionC"
    }
]
